
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Guess this Movie: 🚢 👩🏻‍❤️‍👨🏻 🌊 💥 💀",
  answer: "Titanic",
  options: [
    "Veera Shima Reddy",
    "Uppena",
    "Happy Holiday",
    "Titanic"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "Guess this Movie: 👨🏾 🌊 🚣🏽‍♂️ 🐅",
  answer: "Life of Pie",
  options: [
    "Noah",
    "Life of Pie",
    "RRR",
    "Liger"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "Guess this Movie: 🐍 🦍 🐅 👦🏽 🌳 📖",
  answer: "Jungle Book",
  options: [
    "Tiger Nageshwar Rao",
    "Jumanji",
    "Jungle Book",
    "NagaValli"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "Guess this Movie: 🔎 🐟 ",
  answer: "Finding Nemo",
  options: [
    "Finding Nemo",
    "The Search",
    "Aqua Man",
    "Life of Fish"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "Guess this Movie: 🦁 👑 🐺 🌳",
  answer: "Lion King",
  options: [
    "Simha",
    "Lion King",
    "The Forest",
    "Varisu"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "Guess this Telugu Movie from 2020: 🌪 🧚‍♀ 🤖 🏞 ✨",
  answer: "Bheeshma",
  options: [
    "Bheeshma",
    "Vakeel Saab",
    "Ala Vaikunthapurramuloo",
    "Sarileru Neekevvaru"
  ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
  question: "Guess this Telugu Movie from 2018: 🏹 🏰 🌟 🔪 💔",
  answer: "Aravinda Sametha Veera Raghava",
  options: [
    "Rangasthalam",
    "Jersey",
    "Aravinda Sametha Veera Raghava",
    "Mahanati"
  ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
  question: "Guess this Telugu Movie from 2020: 🍽 🍚 🎶 🥁 💕",
  answer: "Middle Class Melodies",
  options: [
    "Middle Class Melodies",
    "Krishna and His Leela",
    "Colour Photo",
    "Uma Maheswara Ugra Roopasya"
  ]
  },
  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "Guess this Movie: 🦁 👑 🐺 🌳",
  answer: "Lion King",
  options: [
    "Simha",
    "Lion King",
    "The Forest",
    "Varisu"
  ]
},  
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "Guess this Movie: 🐍 🦍 🐅 👦🏽 🌳 📖",
  answer: "Jungle Book",
  options: [
    "Tiger Nageshwar Rao",
    "Jumanji",
    "Jungle Book",
    "NagaValli"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 11,
  question: "Guess this Movie: 🚢 👩🏻‍❤️‍👨🏻 🌊 💥 💀",
  answer: "Titanic",
  options: [
    "Veera Shima Reddy",
    "Uppena",
    "Happy Holiday",
    "Titanic"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 12,
  question: "Guess this Movie: 👨🏾 🌊 🚣🏽‍♂️ 🐅",
  answer: "Life of Pie",
  options: [
    "Noah",
    "Life of Pie",
    "RRR",
    "Liger"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 13,
  question: "Guess this Movie: 🐍 🦍 🐅 👦🏽 🌳 📖",
  answer: "Jungle Book",
  options: [
    "Tiger Nageshwar Rao",
    "Jumanji",
    "Jungle Book",
    "NagaValli"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 14,
  question: "Guess this Movie: 🔎 🐟 ",
  answer: "Finding Nemo",
  options: [
    "Finding Nemo",
    "The Search",
    "Aqua Man",
    "Life of Fish"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 15,
  question: "Guess this Movie: 🦁 👑 🐺 🌳",
  answer: "Lion King",
  options: [
    "Simha",
    "Lion King",
    "The Forest",
    "Varisu"
  ]
},  {
  numb: 16,
  question: "Guess this Movie: 🚢 👩🏻‍❤️‍👨🏻 🌊 💥 💀",
  answer: "Titanic",
  options: [
    "Veera Shima Reddy",
    "Uppena",
    "Happy Holiday",
    "Titanic"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 17,
  question: "Guess this Movie: 👨🏾 🌊 🚣🏽‍♂️ 🐅",
  answer: "Life of Pie",
  options: [
    "Noah",
    "Life of Pie",
    "RRR",
    "Liger"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 18,
  question: "Guess this Telugu Movie from 2018: 🕵‍♂ 📁 🕶 💼 🤐",
  answer: "Goodachari",
  options: [
    "KGF: Chapter 1",
    "Aravinda Sametha Veera Raghava",
    "Goodachari",
    "Mahanati"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 19,
  question: "Guess this Movie: 🔎 🐟 ",
  answer: "Finding Nemo",
  options: [
    "Finding Nemo",
    "The Search",
    "Aqua Man",
    "Life of Fish"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 20,
  question: "Guess this Telugu Movie from 2019: 🌾 🏏 🚴‍♂ 🎖 🥇",
  answer: "Jersey",
  options: [
    "Rangasthalam",
    "Jersey",
    "Mahanati",
    "Arjun Reddy"
  ]
},
]

/*


  
*/